<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on (def Think humble, think free) --&gt; </title>
    <link>https://mallozup.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on (def Think humble, think free) --&gt; </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 14:13:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mallozup.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Design: 01 nREPL clojure</title>
      <link>https://mallozup.github.io/posts/systems-draw-01-nrepl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 14:13:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mallozup.github.io/posts/systems-draw-01-nrepl/</guid>
      <description>Meta: This blog post is based on commit: https://github.com/nrepl/nrepl/commit/21a3200a5dee737efa0dca7529cd2b69b41c7644 This the 2nd entry of unconventional systems design.
nREPL The nREPL consist of different (github) repositories: the nREPL server, the clients and middleware extensions.
The &amp;ldquo;unconventional map&amp;rdquo; I draw for nREPL it should give most of the key ponts to understand nREPL general architecture. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t cover all the details and I think one could draw different maps for the specifics components interactions which will go more in details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartofclojure</title>
      <link>https://mallozup.github.io/posts/heartofclojure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 18:39:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mallozup.github.io/posts/heartofclojure/</guid>
      <description>A courageous conference? In the train to Belgium, I was asking me: What is to be a developer? I&amp;rsquo;m a remote developer but during the years, my answer to this question has always changed; like when you revisit a city in different times of your life.
With a superficial mindset, people might think that a developer is just a person who write code, and our industry it might push people to think like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Design: 00-Terraform-libvirt</title>
      <link>https://mallozup.github.io/posts/systems-draw-00/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 18:25:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mallozup.github.io/posts/systems-draw-00/</guid>
      <description>The first 00 unconventional series of Software design.
Meta:  Project: https://github.com/dmacvicar/terraform-provider-libvirt Description:Terraform provider to provision infrastructure with Linux&amp;rsquo;s KVM using libvirt) Language: golang  I&amp;rsquo;m attempting to draw Software architecture in a unconventional way, because I think describing software with predifined models is somehow restrictive. Here is an humble tentative:
Analysis: We have 3 layers of abstraction:
First perspective (number 1 in the picture), the data model and flow in highlevel manner:  terraform-libvirt take as input an HCL file, and transform it in XML format which will then consumed by Libvirt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>